 
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " Understand environmental issues",
    answer: "Environmental Science (BSES)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: " Determine the property boundaries and elevation.",
    answer: "Geodetic Engineering (BSGE), Geological Engineering (BSGeoE), and Mining Engineering",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 3,
    question: " Inspect marine equipment and machinery in order to draw up work requests and job specifications.",
    answer: "Marine Engineering (BSMarE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: " Learn the principles of mathematics and logic to a plethora of functions",
    answer: "Computer Science (BSCS)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " Examine plant, animal, or human genetics and the relationship between them",
    answer: "Molecular Biology (BS Molecular Biology)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: " Fix mechanical problems",
    answer: "Mechanical Engineering (BSME)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: " Learn about the importance of oil and petroleum to the environment",
    answer: "Petroleum Engineering (BSPetE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: " Study the volts and watts",
    answer: "Electrical Engineering (BSEE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: " Know technical analysis of petroleum",
    answer: "Petroleum Engineering (BSPetE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: " Collect measurements of the surface of the earth.",
    answer: "Geodetic Engineering (BSGE) AND Geological Engineering (BSGeoE) AND Mining Engineering (BSME)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 11,
    question: " Analyze air, water, and soil samples",
    answer: "Environmental Science (BSES)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: " Develop programs for communication systems.",
    answer: "Electronics and Communications Engineering (BSECE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: " Guide a patient through their recovery",
    answer: "Nursing (BSN)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 14,
    question: " Study the diverse field such as groundwater resources",
    answer: "Geodetic Engineering (BSGE) AND Geological Engineering (BSGeoE) AND Mining Engineering (BSME)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: " Reduce the risk of chronic disease leading to overall health and well-being.",
    answer: "Nutrition and Dietetics (BS Nutrition and Dietetics)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  

  {
    numb: 16,
    question: " Learn how to use X-rays, CT scanners, and MRI ",
    answer: "Radiologic Technology (BS Rad Tech)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 17,
    question: " Study how power and energy works",
    answer: "Electrical Engineering (BSEE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 18,
    question: " Analyze, plan, design, install, operate and maintain digital devices",
    answer: "Computer Engineering (BSCpE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 19,
    question: " Organize electronic devices.",
    answer: "Electronics and Communications Engineering (BSECE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 20,
    question: " Work with physicians to evaluate images",
    answer: "Radiologic Technology (BS Rad Tech)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  

  {
    numb: 21,
    question: " Convert raw metal into a usable format",
    answer: "Metallurgical Engineering (BSMetE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 22,
    question: " Participate in real-time video conferencing.",
    answer: "Electronics and Communications Engineering (BSECE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 23,
    question: " Make new products/materials (metals, devices, ceramics, plastics)",
    answer: "Materials Engineering (BSMatE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 24,
    question: " Conduct physical exams and check a patient’s vital signs",
    answer: "Nursing (BSN)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 25,
    question: " Plan and implement nutrition programs",
    answer: "Nutrition and Dietetics (BS Nutrition and Dietetics)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  

  {
    numb: 26,
    question: " Investigate the utility of physics laws and theories in industrial applications for large-scale commercialization",
    answer: "Physics (BS Physics) and Applied Physics (BS Applied Physics)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 27,
    question: " Learn more in-flight activities",
    answer: "Aeronautical Engineering (BS AeroE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 28,
    question: " Help people to recover from injury to regain their skills",
    answer: "Occupational Therapy (BSOT)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 29,
    question: " Develop tests used to detect diseases, and genetic disorders",
    answer: "Chemistry (BS Chemistry)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 30,
    question: " Transform metals into a high-performance alloy",
    answer: "Metallurgical Engineering (BSMetE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  

  {
    numb: 31,
    question: " Design marine apparatus and equipment.",
    answer: "Marine Engineering (BSMarE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 32,
    question: " Plan public works projects such as buildings, bridges, and dams.",
    answer: "Civil engineering (BSCE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 33,
    question: " Develop  process and test materials used to create a wide range of products",
    answer: "Materials Engineering (BSMatE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 34,
    question: " Advise other healthcare professionals about safe and effective medicines use",
    answer: "Pharmacy (BS Pharmacy)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 35,
    question: " Study how the machine works",
    answer: "Mechanical Engineering (BSME)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  

  {
    numb: 36,
    question: " Manage construction engineers, contractors, and geotechnical engineers.",
    answer: "Geodetic Engineering (BSGE) AND Geological Engineering (BSGeoE) AND Mining Engineering (BSME)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 37,
    question: " Improve old materials.",
    answer: "Ceramic Engineering (BSCerE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 38,
    question: " Increase productivity by managing people.",
    answer: "Industrial Engineering (BSIE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 39,
    question: " Explore electricity, magnetism, thermodynamics, and mechanics",
    answer: "Physics (BS Physics) and Applied Physics (BS Applied Physics)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 40,
    question: " Know about food safety and quality assurance",
    answer: "Food Technology (BS Food Technology)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  

  {
    numb: 41,
    question: " Design and developed some new biological equipment and devices such as machines for surgery or diagnosing for medical purposes",
    answer: "Biological Engineering (BSBE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 42,
    question: " Explore the history of our planet and how it changed over the period of time",
    answer: "Geology (BS Geology)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 43,
    question: " Take blood to check oxygen levels and other results",
    answer: "Respiratory Therapy (BSRT)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 44,
    question: " Develop economical and commercial skills and processes",
    answer: "Chemical Engineering (BSChE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 45,
    question: " Study marine navigation",
    answer: "Marine Transportation (BSMT)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  

  {
    numb: 46,
    question: " Create mathematical modeling",
    answer: "Mathematics (BS Mathematics) and Applied Mathematics (BS Applied Mathematics)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 47,
    question: " Study the process of mining",
    answer: "Geodetic Engineering (BSGE) AND Geological Engineering (BSGeoE) AND Mining Engineering (BSME)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 48,
    question: " Explore computer-based information systems",
    answer: "Information Technology (BSIT) and Information Systems (BSIS)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 49,
    question: " Study different kinds of metals",
    answer: "Metallurgical Engineering (BSMetE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 50,
    question: " Learn more in Geoscience",
    answer: "Petroleum Engineering (BSPetE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  

  {
    numb: 51,
    question: " Analyze test results to determine the strength of new products and materials",
    answer: "Ceramic Engineering (BSCerE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 52,
    question: " Explore more about medications ",
    answer: "Pharmacy (BS Pharmacy)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 53,
    question: " Develop mechanical structures",
    answer: "Mechanical Engineering (BSME)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 54,
    question: " Study genetic mutations in organisms that lead to diseases",
    answer: "Chemistry (BS Chemistry)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 55,
    question: " Know how machines work inside buildings",
    answer: "Mechanical Engineering (BSME)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  

  {
    numb: 56,
    question: " Learn how to use medical equipment",
    answer: "Medical Technology (BS Med Tech)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 57,
    question: " Study the principles and history of physics",
    answer: "Physics (BS Physics) and Applied Physics (BS Applied Physics)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 58,
    question: " Learn more in the pharmaceutical field",
    answer: "Biological Engineering (BSBE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 59,
    question: " To instill healthy eating habits",
    answer: "Nutrition and Dietetics (BS Nutrition and Dietetics)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 60,
    question: " Help physicians identify illnesses and injuries.",
    answer: "Radiologic Technology (BS Rad Tech)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  

  {
    numb: 61,
    question: " Reviews normal development of communication behavior",
    answer: "Speech-Language Pathology",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 62,
    question: " Set standards for producing, packaging, and marketing food.",
    answer: "Food Technology (BS Food Technology)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 63,
    question: " Identify and utilize information in technology",
    answer: "Information Technology (BSIT) and Information Systems (BSIS)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 64,
    question: " Process, evaluate, and understand the numerical information in our society.",
    answer: "Mathematics (BS Mathematics) and Applied Mathematics (BS Applied Mathematics)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 65,
    question: " Learn the activities related to the production of hydrocarbon",
    answer: "Petroleum Engineering (BSPetE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  

  {
    numb: 66,
    question: " Develop new solutions for a wide variety of  technical problems",
    answer: "Biological Engineering (BSBE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 67,
    question: " Conduct physics research to develop new technologies",
    answer: "Physics (BS Physics) and Applied Physics (BS Applied Physics)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 68,
    question: " Study and produced new chemicals from bacteria",
    answer: "Biological Engineering (BSBE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 69,
    question: " Design equipment/materials to use in building structures",
    answer: "Materials Engineering (BSMatE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 70,
    question: " Learn more about chemicals, foods, drugs, etc.",
    answer: "Chemical Engineering (BSChE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  

  {
    numb: 71,
    question: " Maintain, repair, modify and inspect aircraft",
    answer: "Aeronautical Engineering (BS AeroE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 72,
    question: " Provide information to diagnose patient illnesses by operating radiologic equipment",
    answer: "Radiologic Technology (BS Rad Tech)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 73,
    question: " Study the properties and structures",
    answer: "Materials Engineering (BSMatE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 74,
    question: "  Learn marine fluvial transport",
    answer: "Marine Transportation (BSMT)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 75,
    question: " Study mineral processing",
    answer: "Geodetic Engineering (BSGE) AND Geological Engineering (BSGeoE) AND Mining Engineering (BSME)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  

  {
    numb: 76,
    question: " Identify and describe component of cells and organisms",
    answer: "Molecular Biology (BS Molecular Biology)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 77,
    question: " Learn hypothesis tests with applications in the real world.",
    answer: "Statistics (BS Stat)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 78,
    question: " Provide nutrition therapy to patients with a variety of health conditions.",
    answer: "Nutrition and Dietetics (BS Nutrition and Dietetics)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 79,
    question: " Learn how to treat a patient with a cardiopulmonary disorder",
    answer: "Respiratory Therapy (BSRT)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 80,
    question: " Learn the essential of our health, quality of life, and survival",
    answer: "Environmental Science (BSES)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  

  {
    numb: 81,
    question: " Identify infectious and non-infectious diseases",
    answer: "Medical Technology (BS Med Tech)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 82,
    question: " Perform first aid techniques",
    answer: "Nursing (BSN)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 83,
    question: " Experience carrying goods and commercial shipping.",
    answer: "Marine Transportation (BSMT)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 84,
    question: " Administer medications and health interventions",
    answer: "Nursing (BSN)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 85,
    question: " Transfer the video through webcasting.",
    answer: "Electronics and Communications Engineering (BSECE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  

  {
    numb: 86,
    question: " Explore computational methods",
    answer: "Mathematics (BS Mathematics) and Applied Mathematics (BS Applied Mathematics)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 87,
    question: " Ride boats, ships, and different kinds of water vehicles.",
    answer: "Marine Engineering (BSMarE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 88,
    question: " Study about software and hardware",
    answer: "Computer Science (BSCS)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 89,
    question: " Examine effects of human actions on the environment",
    answer: "Environmental Science (BSES)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 90,
    question: " Practice radiation protection techniques",
    answer: "Radiologic Technology (BS Rad Tech)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  

  {
    numb: 91,
    question: " Determine the quality and sanitation of private and industrial water supplies",
    answer: "Sanitary Engineering (BSSE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 92,
    question: " Plan and optimize manufacturing processes",
    answer: "Industrial Engineering (BSIE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 93,
    question: " Help patients with communication disorders",
    answer: "Speech-Language Pathology",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 94,
    question: " Participate in natural and experimental sciences",
    answer: "Chemical Engineering (BSChE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 95,
    question: " Conduct tests in computer systems, processors, etc.",
    answer: "Computer Engineering (BSCpE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  

  {
    numb: 96,
    question: " Learn about the necessary skills and knowledge for health care",
    answer: "Nursing (BSN)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 97,
    question: " Experience explaining options about giving birth in a hospital or at home",
    answer: "Midwifery (BS Midwifery)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 98,
    question: " Study how humans impact the Earth",
    answer: "Geology (BS Geology)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 99,
    question: " Develop and manage some electrical applications and equipment",
    answer: "Electrical Engineering (BSEE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 100,
    question: " Develop hardware and software",
    answer: "Computer Engineering (BSCpE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  

  {
    numb: 101,
    question: " Help someone to prevent or live better with injury, illness, or disability",
    answer: "Occupational Therapy (BSOT)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 102,
    question: " Process for the control of soil quality",
    answer: "Sanitary Engineering (BSSE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 103,
    question: " Learn more about environmental food production",
    answer: "Biological Engineering (BSBE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 104,
    question: " Learn how to assimilate new knowledge needed for the design",
    answer: "Civil engineering (BSCE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 105,
    question: " Learn matrices and other basic notions",
    answer: "Mathematics (BS Mathematics) and Applied Mathematics (BS Applied Mathematics)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 106,
    question: " Grow bacteria to determine product effectiveness",
    answer: "Molecular Biology (BS Molecular Biology)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 107,
    question: " Test heat resistance of the materials.",
    answer: "Ceramic Engineering (BSCerE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 108,
    question: " Transport people thru waterways vehicles",
    answer: "Marine Transportation (BSMT)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 109,
    question: " Process crude oil for the production",
    answer: "Petroleum Engineering (BSPetE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 110,
    question: " Design systems for remediation of water or air.",
    answer: "Sanitary Engineering (BSSE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 111,
    question: " Research how the body’s functions are affected by nutrient supply",
    answer: "Nutrition and Dietetics (BS Nutrition and Dietetics)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 112,
    question: " Analyze the structure of molecules",
    answer: "Molecular Biology (BS Molecular Biology)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 113,
    question: " Understand statistics",
    answer: "Statistics (BS Stat)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 114,
    question: " Learn the normal curve",
    answer: "Statistics (BS Stat)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 115,
    question: " Know how metallic bonds formed",
    answer: "Metallurgical Engineering (BSMetE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
 
  {
    numb: 116,
    question: " Design chemical processes",
    answer: "Chemical Engineering (BSChE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 117,
    question: " Develop satellites and rovers",
    answer: "Aeronautical Engineering (BS AeroE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 118,
    question: " Care for infants and children",
    answer: "Midwifery (BS Midwifery)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 119,
    question: " Transport people or goods via waterways",
    answer: "Marine Transportation (BSMT)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 120,
    question: " Learn more about Aircraft, Spacecraft, etc.",
    answer: "Aeronautical Engineering (BS AeroE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
 
  {
    numb: 121,
    question: " Study chemicals and materials and how they behave under different conditions.",
    answer: "Chemistry (BS Chemistry)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 122,
    question: " Develop new food, flavors, and colors.",
    answer: "Food Technology (BS Food Technology)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 123,
    question: " Learn graphical information",
    answer: "Mathematics (BS Mathematics) and Applied Mathematics (BS Applied Mathematics)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 124,
    question: " Help people who have physical, sensory, or cognitive problems.",
    answer: "Occupational Therapy (BSOT)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 125,
    question: " Listen to patients and analyze their physical and emotional needs ",
    answer: "Nursing (BSN)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
 
  {
    numb: 126,
    question: " Formulate solutions to lessen the impact of disasters",
    answer: "Geology (BS Geology)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 127,
    question: " Make artificial intelligence",
    answer: "Computer Science (BSCS)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 128,
    question: " Explore algorithm formulation",
    answer: "Computer Science (BSCS)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 129,
    question: " Learn more about Electricity",
    answer: "Electrical Engineering (BSEE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 130,
    question: " Develop new ways to use existing materials",
    answer: "Materials Engineering (BSMatE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
 
  {
    numb: 131,
    question: " Study programming concepts",
    answer: "Computer Science (BSCS)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 132,
    question: " Perform experiments with the properties of chemical substances",
    answer: "Chemistry (BS Chemistry)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 133,
    question: " Formulate practical problems",
    answer: "Mathematics (BS Mathematics) and Applied Mathematics (BS Applied Mathematics)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 134,
    question: " Extract DNA and RNA from cells and tissues",
    answer: "Molecular Biology (BS Molecular Biology)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
 
  {
    numb: 135,
    question: " Control and regulate stream, lake, tidal water pollution.",
    answer: "Sanitary Engineering (BSSE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 136,
    question: " Study human communications",
    answer: "Speech-Language Pathology",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 137,
    question: " Collect and analyze geological information like soil or rock data",
    answer: "Geology (BS Geology)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 138,
    question: " Develop techniques for materials that can be resisted in heat.",
    answer: "Ceramic Engineering (BSCerE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 139,
    question: " Administer therapeutic doses of radiation to treat cancer",
    answer: "Radiologic Technology (BS Rad Tech)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
 
  {
    numb: 140,
    question: " Take care of a mother and a newborn baby",
    answer: "Midwifery (BS Midwifery)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 141,
    question: " Study how genetic traits are carried through successive generations",
    answer: "Chemistry (BS Chemistry)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 142,
    question: " Study computer programming",
    answer: "Computer Engineering (BSCpE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 143,
    question: " Improve some invented/developed chemicals, drugs, etc.",
    answer: "Chemical Engineering (BSChE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 144,
    question: " Be in computer data developing",
    answer: "Computer Engineering (BSCpE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
 
  {
    numb: 145,
    question: " To be aware of how food and nutrition affect human health.",
    answer: "Nutrition and Dietetics (BS Nutrition and Dietetics)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 146,
    question: " Test mechanical, thermal, sensors, and devices.",
    answer: "Mechanical Engineering (BSME)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 147,
    question: " Collect and analyze meaningful data",
    answer: "Statistics (BS Stat)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 148,
    question: " Be in a business administration",
    answer: "Industrial Engineering (BSIE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 149,
    question: " Help elders to recover from a stroke or deal with Alzheimer’s disease",
    answer: "Occupational Therapy (BSOT)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
 
  {
    numb: 150,
    question: " Repair marine apparatus and equipment.",
    answer: "Marine Engineering (BSMarE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 151,
    question: " Learn how humans impact environmental issues",
    answer: "Environmental Science (BSES)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 152,
    question: " Experiment with new products to use for structures",
    answer: "Materials Engineering (BSMatE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 153,
    question: " Study Statistical inference",
    answer: "Statistics (BS Stat)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 154,
    question: " Study computer and computing concepts",
    answer: "Computer Science (BSCS)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
 
  {
    numb: 155,
    question: " Analyze data in order to determine the feasibility of a product proposal.",
    answer: "Marine Engineering (BSMarE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 156,
    question: " Ensure that all lab tests performed are accurate",
    answer: "Medical Technology (BS Med Tech)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 157,
    question: " Design machinery and tools.",
    answer: "Ceramic Engineering (BSCerE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 158,
    question: " Conduct and develop new chemicals, foods, etc.",
    answer: "Chemical Engineering (BSChE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 159,
    question: " Help people with disabilities to participate in school and social situations",
    answer: "Occupational Therapy (BSOT)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
 
  {
    numb: 160,
    question: " Collect, filter, process, create and distribute data.",
    answer: "Information Technology (BSIT) and Information Systems (BSIS)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 161,
    question: " Investigate the causes of climate change",
    answer: "Geology (BS Geology)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 162,
    question: " Learn how to communicate effectively in both oral and written language",
    answer: "Speech-Language Pathology",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 163,
    question: " Help people to get the best results from their medications",
    answer: "Pharmacy (BS Pharmacy)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 164,
    question: " Help people who suffer from chronic respiratory diseases",
    answer: "Respiratory Therapy (BSRT)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
 
  {
    numb: 165,
    question: " Work to eliminate, prevent, or fix pollution",
    answer: "Environmental Science (BSES)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 166,
    question: " Display and describe data",
    answer: "Statistics (BS Stat)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 167,
    question: " Learn more about Construction Stage Analysis",
    answer: "Civil engineering (BSCE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 168,
    question: " Prepare and dispense prescriptions",
    answer: "Pharmacy (BS Pharmacy)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 169,
    question: " Develop new drugs and medications",
    answer: "Chemistry (BS Chemistry)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
 
  {
    numb: 170,
    question: " Experience extracting gaseous and liquid hydrocarbon",
    answer: "Petroleum Engineering (BSPetE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 171,
    question: " Control the safe operation on waterways",
    answer: "Marine Transportation (BSMT)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 172,
    question: " Help women in their childbearing cycle and birthing process",
    answer: "Midwifery (BS Midwifery)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 173,
    question: " Collect and analyze samples of blood, tissue, and body fluids",
    answer: "Medical Technology (BS Med Tech)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 174,
    question: " Experience how to deliver a baby",
    answer: "Midwifery (BS Midwifery)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
 
  {
    numb: 175,
    question: " Design Webpage",
    answer: "Information Technology (BSIT) and Information Systems (BSIS)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 176,
    question: " Develop new features after updating new software",
    answer: "Computer Engineering (BSCpE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 177,
    question: " Experiment with foods, and make new ways of preparing them.",
    answer: "Food Technology (BS Food Technology)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 178,
    question: " Evaluate the operation of marine equipment during shakedown cruises.",
    answer: "Marine Engineering (BSMarE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 179,
    question: " Develop new equipment that harvests and process our food",
    answer: "Biological Engineering (BSBE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
 
  {
    numb: 180,
    question: " Study Databases",
    answer: "Information Technology (BSIT) and Information Systems (BSIS)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 181,
    question: " Evaluate clients comprehensively and implement treatment plans.",
    answer: "Speech-Language Pathology",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 182,
    question: " Learn more about the maintenance of infrastructure",
    answer: "Civil engineering (BSCE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 183,
    question: " Work to eliminate waste of time, money, energy, and materials",
    answer: "Industrial Engineering (BSIE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 184,
    question: " Explore mechanics, heat, light, sound, electricity, and magnetism",
    answer: "Physics (BS Physics) and Applied Physics (BS Applied Physics)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
 
  {
    numb: 185,
    question: " To learn maternity care",
    answer: "Midwifery (BS Midwifery)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 186,
    question: " Design methods of separating metal from the rest of the components",
    answer: "Metallurgical Engineering (BSMetE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 187,
    question: " Explore various natural phenomena that exist in Earth's Spheres",
    answer: "Geology (BS Geology)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 188,
    question: " Be in the manufacturing and testing of the electrical equipment",
    answer: "Electrical Engineering (BSEE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 189,
    question: " Learn how to transform resources into useful goods and services",
    answer: "Industrial Engineering (BSIE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
 
  {
    numb: 190,
    question: " Monitor how metals perform and evaluate how they deteriorate.",
    answer: "Metallurgical Engineering (BSMetE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 191,
    question: " Study the functional and organic disorders that may affect communications.",
    answer: "Speech-Language Pathology",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 192,
    question: " Go to project sites to monitor constructions",
    answer: "Civil engineering (BSCE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 193,
    question: " Inform stakeholders, company employees, or other relevant parties of environmental issues.",
    answer: "Sanitary Engineering (BSSE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 194,
    question: " Understand the physiology of the cell",
    answer: "Molecular Biology (BS Molecular Biology)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
 
  {
    numb: 195,
    question: " Examine sample water, sewage, and industrial waste.",
    answer: "Sanitary Engineering (BSSE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 196,
    question: " Help prevent harmful drug interactions",
    answer: "Pharmacy (BS Pharmacy)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 197,
    question: " Diagnose and treat various diseases",
    answer: "Medical Technology (BS Med Tech)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 198,
    question: " Perform clinical laboratory procedures",
    answer: "Medical Technology (BS Med Tech)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 199,
    question: " Ensure that the  medicines and doses are correct",
    answer: "Pharmacy (BS Pharmacy)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 200,
    question: " Maintain internet services.",
    answer: "Electronics and Communications Engineering (BSECE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 201,
    question: " Design machines",
    answer: "Mechanical Engineering (BSME)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 202,
    question: " Help persons with disabilities",
    answer: "Occupational Therapy (BSOT)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 203,
    question: " Design transportation and buildings",
    answer: "Civil engineering (BSCE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 204,
    question: " To participate in space applications and explorations",
    answer: "Aeronautical Engineering (BS AeroE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 205,
    question: " Improve the quality of some products and services",
    answer: "Industrial Engineering (BSIE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
 
  {
    numb: 206,
    question: " Design equipment for the forming and firing of ceramic materials.",
    answer: "Ceramic Engineering (BSCerE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 207,
    question: " Conceptualize, develop, and design a safe, economical, and ethical utilization of electrical energy.",
    answer: "Electrical Engineering (BSEE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 208,
    question: " Learn about Flight Mechanics and Control Systems.",
    answer: "Aeronautical Engineering (BS AeroE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 209,
    question: " Test how well your lungs work",
    answer: "Respiratory Therapy (BSRT)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 210,
    question: " Interview and examine patients with breathing or cardiopulmonary disorders",
    answer: "Respiratory Therapy (BSRT)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
 
  {
    numb: 211,
    question: " Focus on mathematics and physical principles, including quantum theory",
    answer: "Physics (BS Physics) and Applied Physics (BS Applied Physics)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 212,
    question: " Service organizations such as broadcasting, entertainment.",
    answer: "Electronics and Communications Engineering (BSECE)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 213,
    question: " Perform diagnostic respiratory care procedure",
    answer: "Respiratory Therapy (BSRT)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 214,
    question: " Focus on the scientific preparation and distribution of food",
    answer: "Food Technology (BS Food Technology)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 215,
    question: " Explore Digital and Information Literacy",
    answer: "Information Technology (BSIT) and Information Systems (BSIS)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
 
  {
    numb: 216,
    question: " Ensure that food remains safe and nutritious",
    answer: "Food Technology (BS Food Technology)",
    options: [
      "1 - Hate it",
      "2 - Dislike it",
      "3 - Neutral",
      "4 - Like it",
      "5 - Love it"
    ]
  },
  

  
];
